You are a profitable
trader. Never ever be dominated by a
[Music]
woman. So that's obviously not how my
morning goes. My morning pretty much
consists of me waking up around 8 7:30
8:00 in the morning and as soon as I
wake up I get started with trading
immediately. I don't have to meditate. I
don't have to drink coffee. I don't have
to read a book. I just go straight into
my office and I start trading. So, let's
see if I can find any trade
opportunities and see where today takes
us. I made a decision last night that I
would die
for just to show the city what it takes
to be alive for it. So, this is the
exciting part of trading, right? No. So,
it's been about an hour and I'm just
waiting for my entry signal. But in the
meantime, I'm literally either talking
to my team questions and calls with my
students inside of my community while
I'm just waiting for this [__] trade
to give me my entry signal. I mean, I
might just take this trade right now.
Honestly, it is a high-risisk trade, but
I just created this brand new high-risk
account. You can tell I just internally
deposited 700,000 literally 10 minutes
ago. And you can tell it is a live
account. It is on a real server.
Everything is under my name. All right,
boys. We're going in. So switching
phones, we are going to take GBP CAD
right now as a sell. So we have about a
60 pip stop loss. We have a 111 pip
takeprofit. Selling this trade because
literally creating the exact same
pattern as Euro USD. You see this shift
to structure. Price retested it. We're
anticipating for a sell. You can see
here on Euro USD, the shift to
structure, the retest, and it's already
having the sell and missed out on this
position. So, we're going to basically
take the exact same trade right here on
GBPCAT. It's a little bit of a high-risk
trade, I'm not going to lie. And I do
see this trade going into some draw
down, maybe like 50% of what I'm going
to risk. And since this is a high-risisk
account, I'll probably risk probably
risk like 7% of it. So, and then we
never place a take profit because we
[__] set and forget. So, that's
basically it. We are currently down
$3,000. I I expect for this to probably
go into draw down like 20 25,000 and
then hopefully be going into profit. All
right, so a little bit of an update of
our morning. So right now it's 10:30 in
the morning. We're up about $8,000 and
I'm interested in entering a new
position. I'm going to enter a new
position right now on Euro USD. This is
going to be on my big boy
account. We're not going to show the
account size because it is a little like
some people are going to think it's not
real and I rather just not even show it.
I have a total of 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8. So
almost a,000 lot exposure on this
position. I mean, we're already up
$10,000. So you can see the difference
in between having a big boy account and
having a look, we're already at $20,000.
So that was literally what, like 2
seconds that we just made. Okay, now
we're back at 20 grand. So like look,
now we're at 30 grand. This shows you
guys the power of having a big boy
account. And I'm doing a very
conservative risk amount on this
account. And there's a difference
between my high-risisk account, which is
a little bit amount of money compared to
my normal account. We're up about 40
grand in basically 2 minutes. I'm going
to break my fast probably in the next 30
minutes. My trainer is going to pull up.
We're going to hit a workout and going
to continue being here in front of the
computer. So, I'll probably be here for
the next 20 30 minutes and see where
that goes. We're off 50 grand, by the
way. Just so I'm about to feed my cat
right now. It's 11:11. Holy [__] That
means we're in profit. No, please. Oh,
yeah. So, on this trade, on the
high-risisk account, we're about 40
grand. And on the other account, we're
down 36 grand. We'll get a quote. We got
to feed my cat. First time walking
outside. This is my 100 lb shepherd
here. So, right around 11:30 in the
morning is where I'll break my fast with
basically straight protein. I have a
full-time chef. cooks me either my three
meals a day cuz you guys been calling me
fat in the comments and I take that
offensive. You know what? Now I'm as
shredded as I've been. And you'll see it
later when we go hit the gym in just a
second. But yeah, I'll break it with
just some eggs, some meat, and then I'll
have one of these coconuts that I get
from one of my trees back here. And I'm
going to cut it with my machete when I'm
done eating. And then I'll drink the
coconut water. Does not get any more
fresh than this. Not that supermarket
[__]
So, one time I actually did this without
moving my hand out of the way and that
[__] literally landed like right there
and I was like, "H, you know what? I
need my thumb for my life." So, you know
what? Every single time I go throw the
machete down now, I would just move my
hand. Last thing I want to do is just
lose a [__]
thumb. I told you it was right there.
Back in my day when I was in Cuba,
right? It's how we used to get
around. M. All right. So, Mac just
pulled up right now. About to hit a
little quick workout. I've been training
with Mac probably for the last 2 3
months. I've had minor results. Good. My
brother chilling. Chilling. Mac the
legend. Let's go. You ready? Get
[Music]
it. [__] What? Yo, you guys call me
[__] Batman, huh?
about now. I got wrecked cuz my boy
[__] met. You know what I'm saying?
Shredded. How do you How do you see like
my progression in the last 2 months?
Like I mean, bro, we've been on point. I
mean, diet's been on point. Cardio's
been on point. Every session we've gone
all in. Everything's going according to
plan. Who Who have you had like the
craziest transformation that you've
seen? Well, I just had a really crazy
one. Speed, the one that that you saw
went viral. I was like everywhere. A
Ross was another big one that I had.
Lacy as well that got some FaZe Clan is
another big one. like what what's the
secret to like having the
transformation, bro? You know what it
is? Nutrition. At the end of the day,
like diet is 90% at least 80% of it, you
know? Um, but I think having a
structured workout routine and having an
actual nutrition plan to follow is
everything, you know? On top of being
held accountable, you know, being held
accountable is is big. Now, people
probably thinking that I'm shooting up,
but I'm not shooting up, bro. That's
like the biggest compliment I say all
the time. Like, if people say you're
shooting up, it's a compliment. Thank
you, man. Pulling out your [__] bro.
Good [__] Now, after this, we're going
to do cold plunge and back to the
office. Oh, trade update. See how the
[__] traders look. So, one of them is
looking like this. So, we're probably
we're probably 50K, which is not bad.
This guy's never not working. 50K. And
then the other one we're up 25K. You got
making gains while making gains, bro.
Get your ass on, man.
One of the main reasons I work out in
slides and in beaches every single day
is because every single time I finish my
workout into the cold plunge, but I can
never get directly into the cold plunge.
I always have to like pull my body down,
get it a little bit colder, and then I
get into the cold plunge. It's kind of
like the biggest flex of my day. Every
single day I get in my pool so I can get
in my cop. If not, I'm not able to get
in. So, and also cuz he's island boy.
Probably like 70° realistically.
Literally, every single day I get in my
pool, cool
down lunch. Before that, trade update.
All right, so we're up right now. So
far, around $80,000.
Oh, [__] I always have to let my feet
cool down even more and then after that
I end up submerging my body fully. So it
does take me a process and I do do the
full 3 minutes but it takes me a [__]
time. Oh bro, stop being a big girl.
Nah, bro. That [__] hurts like a
[__] bro. I want to see you.
All right. Well, this is not good.
Hey, hey, hey, hey. Don't touch my
submerge now or go straight into stop
loss.
I don't want stop loss, dude.
Yeah. All right. Look, we're going to
time it. So, it took me 2 minutes to get
in. We're going to stop it and reset.
Start 3 minutes right now. No, I don't
put my full body in. I'm I'm I'm not
that guy yet. What's one piece of advice
you could give someone that's going
through an uncomfortable moment?
Hard times don't last. Hard men do.
Wait, is that how it goes? How does it
go? Hard times don't last. Hard people
do. No, that's not how it goes either.
[__] How does it go? Diamonds are built
under pressure.
I got another one. Okay. Who's going to
carry the boat?
That's you. You think about it too much.
Don't think about the pain. Think about
the glory.
This is what I want to see right here.
Not bad. So, after this, we'll probably
we're going to get some food. Chef is
almost done cooking up and I probably
have a couple more meetings until like
4:00, 5:00. And then I usually usually
probably nap around that time, but I
think I'm going to go out on the boat
today with the boys. I don't have
anything else for the day. But I spend
90% of my day at my house. I don't go
out to eat. My food is here. I don't go
out to hit the gym. My gym is here. I
don't go out to work. My work is like my
whole entire day is here. My whole team
comes here every single day. So I try
and find a reason to leave the house
sometimes because I've kind of created
an environment where I don't have to
leave everything. So there'll be like 3
4 days that I just won't leave the house
at all. I'll be like, "Holy shit." Like,
when was the last time I drove a car?
But when I do drive it, I drive it for
real. Alex is just a chill guy. I'm just
a [__] chill
guy. Freezing my balls
[Music]
off just to show you guys. 5 minutes.
Actually, now time to eat. All right,
boys. Just finished the meetings and
solid trade. We're currently up $85,000
on EuroUSD and on our other account it's
$85,000. You guys can see here Euro USD
having a very nice push and GBP having a
very nice push. So I'm pretty much done
for the day and I called the boys. Boys
are down for the boat at 5. So basically
in the next hour it's traffic hour.
Probably take us like 30 minutes to get
there. 30 40 minutes. Going to go have a
boat day with the boys. Come back later
tonight. Hit some cardio, playing
basketball, and see where the day takes
us. So, let's go. So, this is probably
the hardest decision of the day. Yeah.
What the [__] do we do? Cullin, we drive
all the time. Bugatti, we haven't driven
the Bugatti in a while. GTR manual
traffic rightand drive, not the plane.
Porsche wise, uncomfortable seats, not
the plane. I forgot I had the clearance.
Who even likes me? I like the doors go
up, right? You know, it makes me feel
like a little bit like a cool guy. We're
going to take the Bugatti. Yeah. Why not
the Beetle? Hell no. Traffic hour, no
AC. [__] might break down. [__] that.
Take it to Bugatti.
Bugatti. All right, boys. So, we're on
our way to the boat. Looking like a
skater, dude. Really? Like a [__]
surfer, bro. [__] yeah. I've never seen
a surfer in a
Bugatti. Oh, we're pulling up on the
fence. Oh [__] All right. All
right. Slow down. See? See? Cool guy.
Hey, he let me go. I guarantee you
there's nothing in the face of the earth
that that man can do to catch me.
There's nothing that guy can Oh no, he
could call for backup and I'm [__] As
long as they don't call for the chopper,
I'm good. Oh, the boys outside that
those are the guys you don't want to
[__] with because these regular cops,
they can't chase you. Those
[__] can chase you till the
wheels fall off. Florida Highway Patrol,
I will stop immediately. Oh [__] I'm
getting [__] pulled over. You pulled
over soon. I'm getting double pulled
over. Probably going to jail right now,
so see what happens. You got your
insurance registration? Yeah, I have my
firearm. Is your license with the
firearm? No, it's on my I I just want to
let you know. It's a nice car, though.
Thank you. You have it, right? Okay.
Just Just have it ready on your screen.
I I won't take your phone. I'll have
them come to you. Sure. What's the top
speed on this car? I'm just curious.
Probably like 300. 300 miles per hour.
That's Yeah. No m. Yeah. 300 m per hour.
I've never gone past like 70 though.
[Music]
[Applause]
Want to [__] with those
guys. My trader friends. Uh uh. Come
over here.
One of my other boys. He's a crypto
trader, George. Friends for my whole
entire life. He's also pulling up. And
then we'll probably pick up one of our
other boys, Benji, somewhere in Kiscape.
So,
not good. But we will continue to set
and forget. My boy George has been my
lifelong friend, also known as my uglier
twin, George. What's up, guys? So, we're
just going to do some weight boarding.
This guy sucks at wakeboarding. Bro, you
suck. I showed him how to wakeboard.
Have you ever wakeboarded before? I've
never wakeboarded. [__] About to find
out. Yeah, I got you, bro. I got you.
Damn, bro. That's a sucker.
[Music]
You're going to have to jump. Sure. Can
you get closer? That's as close as I'm
getting, brother. Come on. Go. Go. Go.
Hurry up.
Why come? Not bad. Not bad. Can you take
me to India?
Dirty cash. I want you. Dirty cash. I
need
you. I need
you. [__] gnarly, dude. All right.
Who's next? Your turn, brother. All
right, let's go.
Oh, wow.
The absolute hooh again.
Look at that. I didn't even [__]
[Music]
[__]
idiot. Make it right.
What are you doing?
[Applause]
No, it's not like that. It's Look at me.
Look at me. Sure. Look at me. Look at
me. I'm the captain now.
We're making
progress. All right, boys.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
[Music]
wait.
Holy [__] Oh my
god. Time for the time for strategy.
Yes. Oh yeah.
do the hour where girls take selfies.
You want to write on it like that? Get
it? No. No. Because no [__] girls
watch this channel. It's just straight
dudes. 99% of my following is dudes.
All right, boys. Market update or day in
the life update. Currently 900 p.m. So,
this is literally the exact perfect time
that I like to look at the markets and
see what it's done. So, 4 hour. Just had
a little rejecting, which is great. GV
CAD. Great continuation sells. Pretty
much it. We're up about 65 on this
account and back to 80,000 on this
account. This trade should make me about
half a million dollars.
[Music]
Yep. Nope. Did you forget we're still
doing a day in the life?
Holy [__] it's
11:00. I just fall asleep like this for
like an hour. So, usually I take a
midday nap. Today I didn't. Just in the
same
spot. You got to hit cardio. You ready
for some balls, ma'am? Ma'am, excuse me.
Come
on. Come
on. All right. This will take me a
minute or two. check in with you just
now. Oh, a little story time for you
guys. I don't know if any of you guys
know or not, but these shoes were kind
of cool back in the day. I used to be a
sneaker head in middle school and these
are Concord 11s. I'll never forget when
I got my first pair in middle school one
day here in Miami. It was pouring and I
was leaving school, I was going to get
picked up by the bus cuz I would go home
in the big yellow buses and it was
raining. And whenever it rains and you
get the bottom of these wet, they get
yellow. They're usually crispy, icy
white. And I was not going to let the
bottom of my brand new Concords get
yellow. So took them off, put them in my
book bag, left the books in school, and
I walked to the bus barefoot. The whole
ride barefoot in my socks. And then from
the bus stop to my parents house, I
walked barefoot. All of that so I
wouldn't get the bottom of my Concords
yellow. And now they're my beers. Just
to play basketball, [__] around. My life
has a full circle sometimes. Doesn't
matter. Well, I don't know if that's a
full circle moment. I think that's just
the turntables have turned. How the
tables have turned. How the turn has
tabled. [__] this up, man. Let's play
some basketball.
[Music]
Yeah. All
right, ladies and gentlemen, and that is
pretty much a wrap to my day. So, it is
currently 1:20 in the morning and I
don't there's like no real end to my day
and there's no real start to my day
because basically right now I just got
out the shower and I'm going to probably
chill here for the next 30 40 minutes.
Same thing, either talking to the
community or watching YouTube videos,
just getting educated, always finding
ways to gain more knowledge while I wait
for a new trade setup. Maybe I'll knock
out and I set an alarm for every single
hour of the night. So, let's say I knock
out at 2:00 in the morning, I'll set an
alarm for 3 and I'll wake up, look at
it. If I have what I want, I'll go back
to sleep. If not, it'll be 4:00. I'll
wake up at 4:00. If I get what I want, I
take the trade. If not, I go back to
sleep. And the pattern just basically
continues throughout the whole entire
London session. and maybe I take the
trade, knock out for 2, three hours,
wake up New York, the whole entire day
continues again. So, I don't really ever
end the day and I don't really ever
start the day. It just keeps going
forever except on the weekends. That's
where I basically catch up on my sleep.
Right now, you guys can see the trade is
basically at $90,000 from where
rejecting there. And yep, now I just
chill here. If the boys are here over
trading London, we would probably go out
drifting or maybe just do something
stupid honestly while we wait for the
markets to give us an opportunity. So
yeah, that's basically what a day in my
life looks like. And let's see what
these markets have to bring tonight.
[Music]